<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide App</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="fragment_food_title">Food</string>
    <string name="fragment_historic_title">Historic</string>
    <string name="fragment_hotels_title">Hotels</string>
    <string name="fragment_popular_title">Popular</string>


    <string-array name="popular_places_names">
        <item name="pupular_sagrada_familia_name">Sagrada Família</item>
        <item name="popular_park_güell">Park Güell</item>
        <item name="popular_la_rambla">La Rambla</item>
        <item name="popular_camp_nou">Camp Nou</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="popular_places_description">
        <item name="popular_sagrada_familia_description">The Basílica i Temple Expiatori de la Sagrada Família i
            s a large unfinished Roman Catholic church in Barcelona, designed by Catalan architect Antoni Gaudí
            (1852–1926). Gaudí\'s work on the building is part of a UNESCO World Heritage Site, and in November
            2010 Pope Benedict XVI consecrated and proclaimed it a minor basilica as distinct from a cathedral,
            which must be the seat of a bishop. In 1882, construction of Sagrada Família started under architect
            Francisco de Paula del Villar. In 1883, when Villar resigned, Gaudí took over as chief architect,
            transforming the project with his architectural and engineering style, combining Gothic and curvilinear
            Art Nouveau forms. Gaudí devoted the remainder of his life to the project, and at the time of his death
            at age 73 in 1926, less than a quarter of the project was complete. Relying solely on private donations,
            Sagrada Familia\'s construction progressed slowly and was interrupted by the Spanish Civil War, only to
            resume intermittent progress in the 1950s. Since commencing construction in 1882, advancements in technologies
            such as computer aided design and computerised numerical control (CNC) have enabled faster progress and construction
            passed the midpoint in 2010. However, some of the project\'s greatest challenges remain, including the construction of
            ten more spires, each symbolising an important Biblical figure in the New Testament. It is anticipated that the building
            can be completed by 2026—the centenary of Gaudí\'s death.</item>
        <item name="popular_park_güell_description">The Park Güell is a public park system composed of gardens and architectonic
            elements located on Carmel Hill, in Barcelona, Catalonia. Carmel Hill belongs to the mountain range of Collserola –
            the Parc del Carmel is located on the northern face. Park Güell is located in La Salut, a neighborhood in the Gràcia
            district of Barcelona. With urbanization in mind, Eusebi Güell assigned the design of the park to Antoni Gaudí,
            a renowned architect and the face of Catalan modernism. The park was built between 1900 and 1914 and was officially
            opened as a public park in 1926. In 1984, UNESCO declared the park a World Heritage Site under "Works of Antoni Gaudí".</item>
        <item name="popular_la_rambla_description">La Rambla is a street in central Barcelona, popular with tourists and locals alike.
            A tree-lined pedestrian mall, it stretches for 1.2 kilometres connecting Plaça de Catalunya in the centre with the Christopher
            Columbus Monument at Port Vell. La Rambla forms the boundary between the quarters of Barri Gòtic, to the east, and El Raval,
            to the west. La Rambla can be crowded, especially during the height of the tourist season. Its popularity with tourists has
            affected the character of the street, with a move to pavement cafes and souvenir kiosks. It has also suffered from the attention
            of pickpockets and especially towards its southern end, sex workers. The Spanish poet Federico García Lorca once said that
            La Rambla was "the only street in the world which I wish would never end."</item>
        <item name="popular_camp_nou_description">Camp Nou is the home stadium of FC Barcelona since its completion in 1957.
            With a seating capacity of 99,354, it is the largest stadium in Spain and Europe, and the second largest association
            football stadium in the world in capacity. It has hosted two European Cup Champions League finals in 1989 and 1999,
            two UEFA Cup Winners Cup finals, four Inter-Cities Fairs Cup final games, five UEFA Super Cup final games, four Copa del Rey
            finals, two Copa de la Liga final games, twenty-one Supercopa de España final games, five matches including the opening game
            of the 1982 FIFA World Cup, two out of four matches at the 1964 European Nations Cup and the football competition final at the
            1992 Summer Olympics.</item>

    </string-array>
</resources>
