<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide App</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="fragment_food_title">Food</string>
    <string name="fragment_historic_title">Historic</string>
    <string name="fragment_hotels_title">Hotels</string>
    <string name="fragment_popular_title">Popular</string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>

    <string-array name="popular_places_names">
        <item name="pupular_sagrada_familia">Sagrada Família</item>
        <item name="popular_park_güell">Park Güell</item>
        <item name="popular_la_rambla">La Rambla</item>
        <item name="popular_camp_nou">Camp Nou</item>
        <item name="popular_tibidabo">Tibidabo</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="popular_places_locations">
        <item name="popular_sagrada_familia">41.403593,2.174444</item>
        <item name="popular_park_guell">41.413533,2.153251</item>
        <item name="popular_la_rambla">41.385535,2.170020</item>
        <item name="popular_camp_nou">41.380507,2.121485</item>
        <item name="popular_tibidabo">41.421891,2.118953</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="popular_places_description">
        <item name="popular_sagrada_familia_description">The Basílica i Temple Expiatori de la Sagrada Família is
            a large unfinished Roman Catholic church in Barcelona, designed by Catalan architect Antoni Gaudí
            (1852–1926). Gaudí\'s work on the building is part of a UNESCO World Heritage Site and in November
            2010 Pope Benedict XVI consecrated and proclaimed it a minor basilica as distinct from a cathedral,
            which must be the seat of a bishop. In 1882, construction of Sagrada Família started under architect
            Francisco de Paula del Villar. In 1883, when Villar resigned, Gaudí took over as chief architect,
            transforming the project with his architectural and engineering style, combining Gothic and curvilinear
            Art Nouveau forms. Gaudí devoted the remainder of his life to the project, and at the time of his death
            at age 73 in 1926, less than a quarter of the project was complete. Relying solely on private donations,
            Sagrada Familia\'s construction progressed slowly and was interrupted by the Spanish Civil War, only to
            resume intermittent progress in the 1950s. It is anticipated that the building
            can be completed by 2026—the centenary of Gaudí\'s death.</item>
        <item name="popular_park_güell_description">The Park Güell is a public park system composed of gardens and architectonic
            elements located on Carmel Hill, in Barcelona, Catalonia. Carmel Hill belongs to the mountain range of Collserola –
            the Parc del Carmel is located on the northern face. Park Güell is located in La Salut, a neighborhood in the Gràcia
            district of Barcelona. With urbanization in mind, Eusebi Güell assigned the design of the park to Antoni Gaudí,
            a renowned architect and the face of Catalan modernism. The park was built between 1900 and 1914 and was officially
            opened as a public park in 1926. In 1984, UNESCO declared the park a World Heritage Site under "Works of Antoni Gaudí".</item>
        <item name="popular_la_rambla_description">La Rambla is a street in central Barcelona, popular with tourists and locals alike.
            A tree-lined pedestrian mall, it stretches for 1.2 kilometres connecting Plaça de Catalunya in the centre with the Christopher
            Columbus Monument at Port Vell. La Rambla forms the boundary between the quarters of Barri Gòtic, to the east, and El Raval,
            to the west. La Rambla can be crowded, especially during the height of the tourist season. Its popularity with tourists has
            affected the character of the street, with a move to pavement cafes and souvenir kiosks. It has also suffered from the attention
            of pickpockets and especially towards its southern end, sex workers. The Spanish poet Federico García Lorca once said that
            La Rambla was "the only street in the world which I wish would never end."</item>
        <item name="popular_camp_nou_description">Camp Nou is the home stadium of FC Barcelona since its completion in 1957.
            With a seating capacity of 99,354, it is the largest stadium in Spain and Europe, and the second largest association
            football stadium in the world in capacity. It has hosted two European Cup Champions League finals in 1989 and 1999,
            two UEFA Cup Winners Cup finals, four Inter-Cities Fairs Cup final games, five UEFA Super Cup final games, four Copa del Rey
            finals, two Copa de la Liga final games, twenty-one Supercopa de España final games, five matches including the opening game
            of the 1982 FIFA World Cup, two out of four matches at the 1964 European Nations Cup and the football competition final at the
            1992 Summer Olympics.</item>
        <item name="popular_tibidabo_description">Tibidabo is a mountain overlooking Barcelona. At 512 metres, it is the tallest mountain
            in the Serra de Collserola. Rising sharply to the north-west, it has views over the city and the surrounding coastline.
            The summit of the mountain is occupied by the Sagrat Cor church and adjacent Tibidabo Amusement Park. The Torre de Collserola
            telecommunications tower is a short walk away. All three are prominently visible from most of the city of Barcelona. Designed
            by Enric Sagnier, the church took 60 years to construct and is topped by a sculpture of the Sacred Heart of Jesus by Josep Miret
            Llopart. Tibidabo can be reached via the Tibidabo Funicular, which was the first of its kind in Spain, and by the Tramvia Blau or
            road. The Transports Metropolitans de Barcelona minibus service 111 connects it to Vallvidrera village and the upper station of
            the Vallvidrera funicular.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="historical_places_names">
        <item name="historical_arc_de_triomf">Arc de Triomf</item>
        <item name="historical_casa_batllò">Casa Batllò</item>
        <item name="historical_hospital_de_sant_pau">Hospital de Sant Pau</item>
        <item name="historical_santa_maria_del_pi">Santa Maria del Pi</item>
        <item name="historical_the_columbus_monument">The Columbus Monument</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="historical_places_locations">
        <item name="historical_arc_de_triomf">41.390971,2.180756</item>
        <item name="historical_casa_batllò">41.391802,2.165077</item>
        <item name="historical_hospital_de_sant_pau">41.391802,2.165077</item>
        <item name="historical_santa_maria_del_pi">41.382327,2.173722</item>
        <item name="historical_the_columbus_monument">41.375886,2.177638</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="historical_places_description">
        <item name="historical_arc_de_triomf_descritption">This archway served as the main entrance during the city\'s 1888 Universal Exhibition.
            Built from sculpted brick and surrounded by statues, including a sculpture representing the city welcoming international visitors
            to the Exhibition. Barcelona\'s Arc de Triomf sits atop Parc Ciutadella and is a beautiful spot for pictures, to stroll, bike ride
            or picnic on the grass next to it. The attraction itself is eye catching but the area surrounding it is what makes it so stunning
            and serene. If you walk towards the water you\'ll be met by bike paths, beautiful gardens and lounging locals and tourists alike in
            Parc Ciutadella.</item>
        <item name="historical_casa_batllò_description">Casa Batlló is a renowned building located in the center of Barcelona and is one of
            Antoni Gaudí’s masterpieces. A remodel of a previously built house, it was redesigned in 1904 by Gaudí and has been refurbished
            several times after that. Gaudí\'s assistants Domènec Sugrañes i Gras, Josep Canaleta and Joan Rubió also contributed to the
            renovation project. The local name for the building is Casa dels ossos (House of Bones), as it has a visceral, skeletal organic
            quality.</item>
        <item name="historical_hospital_de_sant_pau_description">The former Hospital de la Santa Creu i Sant Pau in the neighborhood of El Guinardó,
            Barcelona is a complex built between 1901 and 1930, designed by the Catalan modernisme architect Lluís Domènech i Montaner.
            Together with Palau de la Música Catalana, it is a UNESCO World Heritage Site. It was a fully functioning hospital until June 2009,
            when the new hospital opened next to it, before undergoing restoration for use as a museum and cultural center, which opened in 2014.</item>
        <item name="historical_santa_maria_del_pi_description">Santa Maria del Pi meaning "St. Mary of the Pine" is a 14th-century Gothic church in Barcelona.
            It is situated on the Plaça del Pi, in the Barri Gòtic district of the city. There are unsubstantiated claims that there was an early Christian
            church on the site in 413. However it is known that in 987 there existed a church outside the city walls and to the west of Barcelona. This was a
            small Romanesque church dedicated to the Blessed Lady of the Pine Tree (one of the titles of the Virgin Mary). The church was built between 1319 and 1391.
            The style of the church was Catalan Gothic, with a single nave almost devoid of ornamentation. However, in 1936 the church was gutted by a fire deliberately
            set by anarchists, who wanted to destroy the building. The church was restored following the end of the Civil War.</item>
        <item name="historical_the_columbus_monument_description">The Columbus Monument is a 60 m tall monument to Christopher Columbus at the lower end of La Rambla.
            It was constructed for the Exposición Universal de Barcelona (1888) in honor of Columbus' first voyage to the Americas. The monument serves as a reminder that
            Christopher Columbus reported to Queen Isabella I and King Ferdinand V in Barcelona after his first trip to the new continent.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="food_names">
        <item name="food_bar_cañete">Bar Cañete</item>
        <item name="food_cova_fumada">Cova Fumada</item>
        <item name="food_restaurante_martínez">Restaurante Martínez</item>
        <item name="food_lomoAlto">LomoAlto</item>
        <item name="food_disfrutar">Disfrutar</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="food_locations">
        <item name="food_bar_cañete">41.379174,2.173073</item>
        <item name="food_cova_fumada">41.379306,2.189236</item>
        <item name="food_restaurante_martínez">41.369604,2.172481</item>
        <item name="food_lomoAlto">41.393595,2.166405</item>
        <item name="food_disfrutar">41.387767,2.153228</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="food_description">
        <item name="food_bar_cañete_description">Cozy up to the bar surrounding the open kitchen at this classic restaurant and local favorite.
            Its extensive offering of both Catalan and Spanish cuisine ranges from the traditional tapa Tortilla de Camarones of Cádiz
            (a fried shrimp fritter) to sautéed veal sweetbreads with artichoke hearts. Note that there are two entrances: one for Bar Cañete
            is on the right, and another for the pricier Cañete Mantel (“tablecloth”) is on the left. Stick with Bar Cañete for the best
            experience. </item>
        <item name="food_cova_fumada_description">One of the oldest restaurants in the beachside neighborhood of La Barceloneta,
            this is the birthplace of the famous “Bomba de la Barceloneta” — a mouth­watering fried mashed potato croquette,
            stuffed with savory ground beef and topped with aioli and hot sauce, which now appears on menus all over the city.
            In addition to the Bombas, try the calamars a la planxa (grilled squid) and grilled sardines (in season in summer).
            If you’re adventurous, add a plate of Cap i Pota, an old-­school Catalan stew of tripe, veal trotters, and veal head in tomato.</item>
        <item name="food_restaurante_martínez_description">There are plenty of places to try paella in Barcelona, but Martínez is the move:
            Perched on the side of Montjuïc with a panoramic view of the city and port, Martínez is far removed from the hubbub of the beach
            district. Famous rice dishes like the señorito paella — garnished with peeled and shelled seafood, which keeps fingers clean —
            and the decadent lobster rice, as well as classic tapas and an inviting oyster bar, should justify the journey.</item>
        <item name="food_lomoAlto_description">In this pork-centric region, beef doesn’t usually play a starring role on menus,
            which makes Lomo Alto even more special. This meat destination is really without compare when it comes to dry-aging,
            with a massive Leonese ox hanging above its reception area that’s well into its 500-day aging journey. Each cut of meat is
            meticulously catalogued and labeled with the age and breed, and the steaks are cooked with precision over charcoal flames on
            custom-made Josper grills. For a special occasion, spring for a 150-day-aged Rubia Gallega T-bone steak, carved tableside.</item>
        <item name="food_disfrutar_description">This restaurant is climbing steadily to the top of Barcelona\'s fine dining pyramid.
            The chef-owners, veterans of the El Bulli kitchen, opened Disfrutar in Barcelona in 2014 and currently hold one Michelin star.
            The modern Mediterranean cuisine and elegant service make for an unmissable experience. </item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="hotel_names">
        <item name="hotel_W">W Barcelona</item>
        <item name="hotel_mandarin_oriental">Mandarin Oriental</item>
        <item name="hotel_hotel_españa">Hotel España</item>
        <item name="hotel_serras">The Serras Hotel</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="hotel_locations">
        <item name="hotel_w">41.368504,2.189333</item>
        <item name="hotel_mandarin_oriental">41.391080,2.166567</item>
        <item name="hotel_hotel_españa">41.379948,2.172785</item>
        <item name="hotel_serras">41.380176,2.180921</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="hotel_description">
        <item name="hotel_w_description">W Barcelona, popularly known as the Hotel Vela due to its shape,
            is a building designed by Ricardo Bofill is located in the Barceloneta district of Barcelona,
            in the expansion of the Port of Barcelona. The hotel is managed by Starwood Hotels and Resorts hotel
            chain and marketed under the brand W Hotels. The building, designed by the architect Ricardo Bofill,
            stands in 7 hectares of land reclaimed from the sea surface in the construction of the new entrance to the harbour.
            It is embedded within the volume of the atrium, has large sea views and natural light, and reflective glass facade
            mixed object and context. It is an example of high-tech architecture in the city. The project included a public place
            open to the sea, a marina and hotel landscape, cosmopolitan icon. The five-star hotel comprises 473 rooms, 67 suites,
            400 employees, a bar located on the rooftop with panoramic city views, a spa and fitness centre, indoor and outdoor pools,
            terraces, beaches, restaurants, rooms dance, and other facilities grouped under a platform of terraces. The hotel provides
            also a gourmet restaurant lead by the Michelin-starred chef, Carles Abellán.</item>
        <item name="hotel_mandarin_oriental_description">Mandarin Oriental is located on Passeig de Gràcia close to a number of Barcelona\’s
            shopping and dining establishments as well as cultural and entertainment venues. The Mandarin Oriental opened in November
            2009 and was designed by a team of Spanish architects and designers: Carlos Ferrater and Joan Trias de Bes (architecture)
            and Patricia Urquiola (interior design). The hotel\’s 98 guest rooms and suites are housed in a re-developed, mid-20th
            Century building that was once home to a bank. Mandarin Oriental also includes The Spa at Mandarin Oriental and five restaurants
            and bars, including Moments, a Catalan restaurant headed up by Carme Ruscalleda, a Michelin starred chef.</item>
        <item name="hotel_españa_description">The Hotel Spain is located on San Pablo Street in Barcelona. Two brothers, Joan and Pau Riba,
            founded the "Fonda España" around 1850, and due to the good reception that the business had, they decided to expand it
            to become the Hotel España and the commission fell to the modernist architect Lluís Domènech i Montaner. Its interior is
            really admirable, the entrance has marble columns, sgraffito and lamps with a modernist style. A large marble fireplace was
            modeled by Eusebio Arnau and made by Alfons Jujol, representing the passage of time between birth and old age, with the
            crowning of a large shield of Spain. In the dining rooms of the restaurant, you can see the great ornamentation they contain,
            a mural in the background with sirens, carved wooden wainscoting with glazed ceramics decorated with shields of Spanish cities,
            stained glass windows and metalwork lamps.</item>]
        <item name="hotel_serras_description">History, art, and pure sensual delights come together majestically at The Serras on Barcelona\'s
            celebrated Gothic quarter. Here, breezes blow off the Mediterranean into large rooms with balconies that offer a front row seat to
            this trendy Barcelona neighborhood. This elegant 5-star GL boutique hotel overlooking the new luxury Port Vell alongside the Mediterranean Sea,
            offers a unique hideaway with a modern understated decor. Ideal for your week-end breaks, business trips and luxury holidays in the heart of
            Barcelona. It boasts a cool, trendy atmosphere, world class amenities and dedicated personal service for a truly memorable hotel experience in
            the first studio of Pablo Picasso on vibrant Barrio Gótico</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
